A Guide to the Joshua Lederberg personal papers, Subject File FA1087
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Subject File, 1
  - Exociol-RCA (Box 41, Folder 41)
  - SRI (Box 41, Folder 42)
  - Security Log - JL (Box 41, Folder 43)
  - Defense Documentation Center (DDC) (Box 41, Folder 44)
  - NASA-SDI Notifications (Box 41, Folder 45)
  - NASA - Science and Technology Information Division - SDI Reports (Box 41, Folder 46)
  - NASA - Science and Technology Information Division - SDI Program (Box 41, Folder 47)
  - NASA - Science and Technology Information Division - Documents Ordered (Box 41, Folder 48)
  - NASA - Science and Technology Information Division - General (Box 41, Folder 49)
  - Classifield Documentation (Box 41, Folder 50)
  - NASA - Headquarters (Box 41, Folder 51)
  - NASA Planetary Atmosphere Subcommittee Space Sciences Steering Committee (Box 41, Folder 52)
  - Conflict of Interest Guidelines (Box 41, Folder 53)
  - NASA Selective Dissemination of Information (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - NASA Headquaters - Advance Program Planning (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - NASA Program Announcement - Decontamination (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - NASA News Releases Miscellaneous (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - NASA Program Announcement - TIROS (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - NASA - Mercury (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - "A Proposal for the Study of Computer Control of External Devices and an Automated Biological Laboratory" - John McCarthy and Joshua Lederberg, Stanford University, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Ames Lab - Young (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Review of the NASA-JPL Spacecraft Sterilization Program (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - JPL Surveyor (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - JPL General Cooperation (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - NASA Lunar Committee (PIP Auxil.) (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - NASA - Planetary HQ Quarantine (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - NASA - HQ Quarantine (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - NASA - Planetary Quarantine, 1972 February (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - NASA - Planetary Quarantine - NAS/NRC Documents, 1969 August 4 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - NASA - Objectives and Models of the Planetary Quarantine Program (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - NASA - HQ Quarantine SRI (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - NASA - Analytical Techniques in Planetary Quarantine - Final Report, 1970 May (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - NASA - Planetary Quarantine - Articles, 1967-1972 (Box 42, Folder 20-22)
  - NASA HQ, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - NASA - Mariner Mars 1971 - Image Proc. (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - NASA - Mariner Expo Report, 1971-1973 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - NASA - Bioscience Program - Exobiology Office of Space Sciences (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - NASA - Biosciences Subcommittee of the Space Sciences Steering Committee, 1960-1962 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - NASA - Office of Space Sciences (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - NASA - Office of Life Sciences, 1959-1961 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - NASA - Bioscience Programs - Office of Space Sciences (Orr Reynolds) (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - NASA - Biosciences Subcommittee of the Space Sciences Steering Committee, 1963 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - NASA - Miscellaneous (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - NASA - Voyager (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - NASA - Lunar and Planetary Missions Board, 1967-1969 (Box 43, Folder 1-23)
  - Burker, Ye. S. (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - WE-WG (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Westinghouse (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - WH (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Willow Run Laboratories (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - WIM-WN (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Frank, G. M. (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Mueller, George (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - WO-WZ (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - X-Y (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - Tikhov, G. A. (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - Safronov, V. S. (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - Safronov, V. V. (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - Reports of Russian Meetings (Box 43, Folder 37)
  - Oparin, A. (Box 43, Folder 38)
  - Niuberg, N. D. (Box 43, Folder 39)
  - Natanson, G. L. (Box 43, Folder 40)
  - Minhustin, Ye. N. USSR (Box 43, Folder 41)
  - NASA - Aerospace Biology USSR (Box 43, Folder 42)
  - Imshenetsky, A. A. (Box 43, Folder 43)
  - Varian (Box 43, Folder 44)
  - Zhukov-Verezhnikov, N. (Box 43, Folder 45)
  - Vsekhsvyatskii, S. K. (Box 43, Folder 46)
  - Vanyushin, B. F. (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - National Institute of Mental Health (NIMH) Summary of Research Areas Active and Pending, 1970 November (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Mental Health (MH) Research Grants in FY 1970, 1969-1970 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - National Institute of Mental Health (NIMH) Summary of Research Areas Active and Pending, 1971 March (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Program Priorities, 1968 July (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - National Institute of Mental Health (NIHM) Council Meeting, 1968 October-November (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - National Advisory Mental Health Council (NAMHC), 1970 September (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - National Advisory Mental Health Council (NAMHC), 1970 June (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - National Institute of Mental Health (NIMH) - Council Meeting, 1970 September (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - NIMH-AMC, 1970 November (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - National Institute of Mental Health, 1971 March (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - National Institute of Mental Health (NIMH) - Council Meeting, 1971 July (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - NIH Applications - Information Notes (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - National Advisory Mental Health Council (NAMHC), 1968 March (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - National Institute of Mental Health (NIMH), 1968 October (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - National Institute of Mental Health (NIMH), 1969 March (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - National Advisory Mental Health Council (NAMHC), 1969 December (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - National Advisory Mental Health Council (NAMHC), 1971 June (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Chem Tech Dendrel (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Viking-JPL, 1973 June-July (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Viking Biol, 1972 December 11 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Viking - Biology Team - Minutes, 1975 September (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - NASA-JPL, 1973 May 7 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Viking - Biology Team - Minutes, 1972 December 11 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Viking - General Correspondence, 1971 April-May (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Viking - Biology Team - General Correspondence, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Viking - Biology Team - Viking '75 Project (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Viking - Biology Team, 1969-1972 (Box 44, Folder 28-34)
  - Viking - General Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 45, Folder 1-6)
  - Viking Policy (PSAC), 1972 November (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - NASA Space Science - Viking, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Viking, 1969 August-November (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Voyager-Ames, 1965 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Viking (Clippings) (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Viking, 1972 February 9 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Viking, 1969 February-July (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Viking, 1973 April (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Viking (Budget) (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Viking Project (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Viking - Site Alteration Working Group, 1971 April (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - NASA HQ Flight Operations, 1972-1976 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Viking-JPL, 1973 March 23 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - VPO-SSG Project - Minutes of Viking Science Steering Group Meeting, 1972 June (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - NASA Meeting - Landing Site, 1975 November (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Viking Landing Site Group (LSG) (LSWG), 1970-1975 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Viking (SORD) (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Viking (LSWG) Pole, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Newsletter - Viking Science Activities, 1970-1973 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Viking Science Management Plan (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Viking LSWG, 1973 April 2 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Viking LSG, 1973 September 18 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Viking LSWG, 1975 February 11 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Viking LSWG, 1973 February (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Viking LSWG, 1973 February 28 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Viking MSPG, 1972 November 7 (Box 46, Folder 9-10)
  - Viking DAT (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Viking Science Regs and Constraints, 1972 May-July (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Viking LSWG, 1972 December 21 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Viking 79 in Situ Expmt NASA (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Viking Project Office Launch Operations (KCS) (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Muller, Richard re: Viking Mission-Real Time Atmosphere Compensation, 1974 December (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Budget - NASA - Viking, 1975 July 9 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - IRL-NASA, 1974-1975 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - NASA 1980-2000 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - ASCA-JL Notes re: Viking 1974 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Mariner Venus-Mercury 1973 Status Bulletin (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Viking Science Activities Newsletter (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Sagan (Jovian Biology) 1974 Horowitz (Quarantine Considerations for Outer Planets Missions) (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Viking - Young and Mac Elroy Biology on the Outer Planets COSPAR Meeting, 1974 June (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Viking Mission to Mars by William R. Corliss, 1974 November (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Viking - Are There Microbers on Mars? Stanford MD, 1974 Fall (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Young, Richard NASA Administration, 1974 August 5 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Mars Sample Return Report, 1974 June (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - Mars Sample Return Hazards (Horowitz Letter), 1974 June (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Viking Landing Site Staff - Site A-1 Certification Procedure Review, 1975 May (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Viking - Landing Site Working Group, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - Viking Lander Science Team Members re: Science Test Status, 1975 March (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - VFT Landing Site Staff Meeting, 1975 July 31 (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - Viking - Discu. Reports, 1975 July (Box 46, Folder 34)
  - Klein, Harold, 1974 October 16 (Box 46, Folder 35)
  - McElroy, Robert D. (NASA), 1975 May 12 (Box 46, Folder 36)
  - Oyama, VI Gas Exchange Experiment, 1975 September 29 (Box 46, Folder 37)
  - Dohahue NASA, 1975 May (Box 46, Folder 38)
  - NAS Panel on Exobiology Report, 1975 August 27 (Box 46, Folder 39)
  - Viking "A" Launch Kennedy Space Center, FL, 1975 August 11 (Box 46, Folder 40)
  - Viking-1 Lander (Box 46, Folder 41)
  - Viking Press (Box 46, Folder 42)
  - Viking - General Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 46, Folder 43)
  - Klein, Harold (Search for Life on Mars: Viking Mission) (Box 46, Folder 44)
  - Viking LSG, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 45)
  - JPL, 1976 June 25 (Box 46, Folder 46)
  - Science News, 1976 June 5-12 (Box 46, Folder 47)
  - Viking - General Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 46, Folder 48-49)
  - Viking Mission Data, 1975 February (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Viking - General Correspondence, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 2-3)
  - Viking, 1976 July (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - First Class 1 Viking, 1976 May 27 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Viking - Landing Site Working Group, 1975 March (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Viking - General Correspondence, 1976 July-August (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - NASA-NASB Denver, 1972 February 4 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Viking, 1974-1975 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - TRW "Hybrid Life Detection Instrument Design Review Data Package: Volume 1, 2, 3 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Viking - Articles (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Viking - Gilbert V. Levin - Articles (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Viking - Articles (Box 47, Folder 13-14)
  - NAS Space Science Board - Plan Quarantine - Denver, 1972 February 3 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Mariner, 1968 September-1969 July (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Mariner 1973 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Mariner Mars 1971 - NASA Headquarters Press Conference of Mariner 9 Science Results, 1972 February 2 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Mariner Mars 1971 - Planetary Quarantine Plan-Project Document Part I - Earl Glahn, 1970 April 13 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Mariner Mars 1971 (Minutes), 1969 February (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - JPL, 1971 October (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - JPL-Mariner, 1971 July (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Mariner Mars 1971 - General Correspondence, 1971 December-1972 January (Box 48, Folder 1-2)
  - JPL, 1971 January-February (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Mariner 9 TV COSPAR MSS (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Mariner Mars 1971, 1971 October 13 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Mariner Mars 1971 Science Regs, 1969 February 3 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Mariner Mars Viking, 1970-1971 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Mariner Mars (MM) 1970, 1970 April (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Mariner Mars 1971, 1970 April-May (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Mariner Mars - General Correspondence, 1969, 1970 October (Box 48, Folder 10-11)
  - Mariner Mars 1971 - General Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 48, Folder 12-35)
  - Mariner Mars 1971 - General Correspondence, 1969 September-December (Box 49, Folder 1-2)
  - Mariner, 1969 August-September (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Mariner 1971, 1969 February (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Mariner 9 Pix P10 (Photographs and Status Bulletins) (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Mariner Mars 1971 Image Analysis Papers (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - JPL - Levinthal (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Mariner Mars 1971 - General Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 49, Folder 8-9)
  - Mariner Mars, 1972 March (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Mariner 4 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Mariner Mars - General Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 49, Folder 12-15)
  - Mars - Mariner 4 Pictures (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Mariner 4, 1972 April 12 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - JPL (Minutes MM 71 Team Meeting), April-June (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Mariner - TV Team Meeting (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Department of Astronomy - New Mexico State University, 1971 November (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Mariner Mars - General Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 49, Folder 21-22)
  - Mariner Mars - Photographs (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Mariner, 1972 December 21 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Mariner - Photographs (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Mariner Mars 1971 - Photographs, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Mariner Mars 1971 - General Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 49, Folder 27-32)
  - Mariner Mars 1971 - Photographs from JPL (Box 49, Folder 33)
  - JPL (MM 1971 TV), 1972 January 19 (Box 49, Folder 34)
  - Mariner Mars 1971 - General Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 49, Folder 35-36)
  - Mariner Mars 1971 - Photographs from NASA (Box 49, Folder 37)
  - Mariner, 1972 April (Box 49, Folder 38)
  - Mariner Viking (Box 49, Folder 39)
  - Mariner Mars 1971 - General Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 49, Folder 40)
  - Articles and Maps (Box 49, Folder 41)
  - Mariner Schedule, 1971 December (Box 49, Folder 42)
  - Viking - Messages from SU-AI, 1976 July, September (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Viking - Photographs (NASA) and Slides, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Viking - Photographs (NASA) (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Viking - General Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 50, Folder 4-5)
  - Project Viking Missions to Mars (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Viking - Magazines, Articles and Clippings, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 7-8)
  - Viking, 1974 September 16 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Viking - Magazines, Articles and Clippings, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Viking, 1976 August (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Viking - Photographs, Articles and Clippings, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - CO Format (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Viking - Biology Team Meeting, 1977 February 28 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Viking - General Correspondence, 1977 April, June (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Levinthal - Viking 3 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - SSB - Mazur Committee Post-Viking, 1977 February (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Viking, 1976 June (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Complex - 1976 September 20 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Viking - General Correspondence, 1976 September, November (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - JPL, 1976 October 27 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Huguenin, Robert re: Mars, 1976 October 11 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Viking - Magazines, Articles and Clippings, 1976-1978 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Viking - General Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 50, Folder 24-25)
  - Mars Science Working Group, 1977 June 20 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - Mars Science Working Group - Expenses (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - Lenetic Clouds Photo (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - Viking Pictures (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - Study Group on Machine Intellegence and Robotics (Viking 3) (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - Viking Biology Lab Results Meeting Ames, Building 299, 1977 May 5-6 (Box 50, Folder 31)
  - Meetings with R. S. Young - NASA-OSS, Boston, 1977 September 14-15 (Box 50, Folder 32)
  - Lederberg Lecture at University of Utah, 1977 March 25 (Box 50, Folder 33)
  - JPL 5/11-13 Mars (Box 50, Folder 34)
  - Viking - General Correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 50, Folder 35)
  - Viking - Magazines, Articles and Clippings, 1977-1978 (Box 50, Folder 36)
  - Viking, 1972 November (Box 50, Folder 37)
  - Viking - Biology - Urgent, 1978 December 12 (Box 50, Folder 38)
  - Viking - Articles (Charles A. Barth), 1969 (Box 50, Folder 39)
  - Viking - General Correspondence, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 40)
  - Viking - General Correspondence, 1971 January-June (Box 50, Folder 41-43)
  - Viking - General Correspondence, 1971 July-1977 (Box 51, Folder 1-13)
  - Viking, 1972 June 25 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Viking - Biology Team Meeting, 1976 March 31 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Viking (Photographs), 1972 July (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Lunar Map, 1977 August 18 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Articles - Lederberg - "Challenge to Biology" (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Viking-Mariner-NASA to: March 31, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Viking - General Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder 20-21)
  - Viking, 1974 October 10 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - ICOM-Mars Mission (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - NASA Viking SORD (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Viking, 1974 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - Viking, 1974 July (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - Viking - General Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 51, Folder 27-29)
  - Viking '75 Project - Certification Test-User Acceptance Test Plan for the Bio Investigation Software (Box 51, Folder 30)
  - Viking '75 Project - VL Biology Investigation Software Requirements Document (Box 51, Folder 31)
  - Viking-JPL, 1974 February 11 (Box 51, Folder 32)
  - Viking SORD, 1974 January (Box 51, Folder 33)
  - Mariner Venus-Mercury Status Bulletin, 1974 July 9 (Box 51, Folder 34)
  - Johnson, Richard (NASA Flight Team Meeting Minutes), 1974 October 16 (Box 51, Folder 35)
  - Viking, 1974 September 26 (Box 51, Folder 36)
  - Viking Biology Team, 1974 May (Box 51, Folder 37)
  - Viking-Mariner, 1972-1974 (Box 51, Folder 38)
  - Johnson, Richard (Viking), 1974 July 12 (Box 51, Folder 39)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - Rockefeller University and Howard Hughes Medical Instittue (HHMI) Collaboration Agreement, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Industry, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - Interinstitutional Relationships (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - Survey of Interinstitutional Collaborations, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Industry - Fugua, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Housing (Box 52, Folder 6-11)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Housing - Loans (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Housing - Sutton House (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Housing - Sutton Terrace, 1983 November 2 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Faculty Housing Programs, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Housing Report (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Housing - Rates (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Housing, 1981-1982 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Hospital - Space, 1981 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Hospital, 1981-1982 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Hospital - Financials, 1987-1989 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Hospital, 1985 May 17 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - MSKCC Survey for CRC Usage (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Hospital - Patient Care Audit Rehabilitation Therapy, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Hospital - Nursing (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Clinical Fellows Program, 1978 (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Hospital, 1978-1982 (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - CRC Review - RU Hospital, 1981 December (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Hospital - GCRC, 1982 June (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU - Invention Status (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU - Iran (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU - Israel (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Karolinska (Box 53, Folder 3A)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - Animal Care Committee (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - Lab Animal Research Center (LARC), 1978-1982 (Box 53, Folder 5-7)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - LARC - Animal Welfare Assurances for Population Council and RU (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - Lab Animal Research Center (LARC) (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Lab Findings (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Land Use (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Land Use Planning Committee Meeting, 1985 June 17 (Box 53, Folder 12-13)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Land Use Planning Committee Meeting, 1985 September-1986 April (Box 53, Folder 14-16)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Land Use, 1979-1986 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - Library Committee (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Library (Box 53, Folder 19-21)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Library - Space Requirements (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Faculty Staff Loans (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Map (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Mass Spectrometric (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Mass Spectrometric Lab, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Mathematics (Box 53, Folder 27-30)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Meetings - Outside Groups (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Millbank Tweed, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 32)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Millbrook (Box 53, Folder 33)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU New Research Building (Box 53, Folder 34-35)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU New Research Building - City Planning Hearing, 1989 September 6 (Box 53, Folder 36)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU-NYC Contracts, 1981 October (Box 53, Folder 37)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - Rodney W. Nichols, 1990 April 3 (Box 53, Folder 38)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - O/P Breakfast, 1990 April 3 (Box 53, Folder 39)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Parking (Box 53, Folder 40)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Parasitology Search (Box 53, Folder 41-44)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU-Peat, Marwick, Main and Com. (Box 53, Folder 45)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Press, 1978-1983 (Box 54, Folder 1-6)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - Status of RU Press and Recommendations for its Future with Bayless (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - RU Priorities (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - Organ and Priorities, 1989 May 15 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - Priorities, 1989 November 1 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - Purchasing Manual (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - Report of the President, 1978-1983 (Box 54, Folder 12-21)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - Reproductive Biology (Box 54, Folder 22-23)
  - Rockefeller University Subject Files - Research Universities Caucus President's Meeting, 1990 January 29 (Box 54, Folder 24)